U.S. Department of Labor Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry 5186
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry
1959
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor
5186
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry, 1959. Collected by George P. Schultz.
5601064
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Schultz, George Pratt, 1920-; United States. Department of Labor
5601064
- Steel Study, The United Steelworkers and Union-Wide Bargaining, George Seltzer, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Steel Study, Report and Study Proposals, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Advanced Course, Labor Institute, Summer (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Steelworkers' Institute Notebook, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Third Annual Steelworkers' Institute, 1949-07-31-1949-08-13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Notebook for Steelworkers' Institute, 1947-06-08-1947-06-21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America Labor Institute, Summer (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Notebook for Steelworkers' Institute, 1948-07-18-1948-07-31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Steel Study, Steelworkers Earnings, Postwar Period, M. Horowitz, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Steel Studies, Interviews, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Steel Study, Strike Experience in Selected Countries, A. Siegel, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Steel Study, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Profiles of Negotiation in Basic Steel, 1937-1959, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Steel Study, Steel Industry, Markets, Technology, Break-Even Points and Financing, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Collective Bargaining in the Basic Steel Industry, A Study of the Public Interest and the Role of Government, 1 of 2, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Collective Bargaining in the Basic Steel Industry, A Study of the Public Interest and the Role of Government, 2 of 2, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Steel Study, Exhibits and Literature of Interest, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Steel Study, Productivity and Price Project, Louis Lister, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Steel Study, Historical Materials, Negotiations, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Steel Study, Fisher's, Steel Output and Wage Losses in Strikes of 1952, 1956, 1959, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Steel Study, Role of Collective Bargaining in Steel, Pattern Setter of Follower, Harold Levinson, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Steel Study, The Influence of Steel Price Increases on Inflation, Frank Norton, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- The Inland Steel Company Case, William F. Whyte, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Job Evaluation Information, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)